Finding Aid for Athletic Department (University of Michigan) records, 1860-[ongoing]
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Sports Information Office, 1860-
  - Scrapbooks (Microfilm)
    - Fan's Football Scrapbooks 1942-1950
      The Fan's Scrapbooks subseries was apparently compiled by a U of M fan and donated to the Athletic Department. The nine volumes cover the years 1942-1950 and are devoted almost exclusively to football. There is some duplication with the Main Series, but the Fan's Scrapbooks contain many items not found in the Main Series, including numerous clippings from out-of-town papers.
      - Vol. 1 1942 (Box 2, Reel 1)
      - Vol. 2 1943 (Box 2, Reel 1)
      - Vol. 3 1944 (Box 2, Reel 1)
      - Vol. 4 1945 (Box 2, Reel 1)
        (Also includes some basketball, hockey, track, and baseball clippings)
      - Vol. 5 1946 (Box 2, Reel 1)
      - Vol. 6 1947 (Box 2, Reel 1)
      - Vol. 7 1948 (Box 2, Reel 2)
      - Vol. 8 1949 (Box 2, Reel 2)
      - Vol. 9 1950 (Box 2, Reel 2)
    - Jay Kleinert Scrapbooks
      The Jay Kleinert Scrapbooks are oversize volumes (approx. 3'x 4' in size) compiled by Kleinert, an avid fan from Jackson, Michigan, and donated to the Athletic Department. They are devoted exclusively to UM football and include newspaper and magazine clippings, some photographs and original artwork by Kleinert. The Kleinert scrapbooks cover the years 1921-1989
      - Vol. 1 1921-1936 (Box 2, Reel 1)
      - Vol. 2 1937-1941 (Box 2, Reel 1)
      - Vol. 3 1942-1949 (Box 2, Reel 1)
      - Vol. 4 1950-1958 (Box 2, Reel 2)
      - Vol. 5 1959-1965 (Box 2, Reel 2)
      - Vol. 6 1966-1970 (Box 2, Reel 2)
      - Vol. 7 1971-1974 (Box 2, Reel 3)
      - Vol. 8 1975 (Box 2, Reel 3)
      - Vol. 9 1976 (Box 2, Reel 3)
        (includes 1976 Orange Bowl)
      - Vol. 10 1977 (Box 2, Reel 3)
        (includes 1977 Rose Bowl)
      - Vol. 11 1978 (Box 2, Reel 4)
        (includes 1978 Rose Bowl)
      - Vol. 12 1979 (Box 2, Reel 4)
        (includes 1979 Rose Bowl)
      - Vol. 13 1980 (Box 2, Reel 4)
        (includes 1981 Rose Bowl)
      - Vol. 14 1981 (Box 2, Reel 4)
        (includes 1981 Bluebonnet Bowl)
      - Vol. 15 1982 (Box 2, Reel 5)
      - Vol. 16 1983 (Box 2, Reel 5)
        (includes 1984 Sugar Bowl)
      - Vol. 17 1984 (Box 2, Reel 5)
        (includes 1984 Holiday Bowl)
      - Vol. 18 1985 (Box 2, Reel 6)
        (includes 1986 Fiesta Bowl)
      - Vol. 19 1986 (Box 2, Reel 6)
        (includes 1987 Rose Bowl)
      - Vol. 20 "Memoirs" 1909-1989 (Box 2, Reel 6)
    - Ben Friedman Scrapbook 1922-1939
      The Ben Friedman scrapbooks were compiled by the Friedman family and loaned to the Athletic Department for microfilming. Friedman, all-American quarterback in 1926, was one of the first nationally prominent Jewish college athletes. The scrapbooks, which cover his high school and professional career as well his Michigan years, are mainly clippings for his hometown Cleveland newspapers and the Jewish press.
      - Vol. 1 (Box 2, Reel 1)
        (High School and UM)
      - Vol. 2 (Box 2, Reel 1)
        (UM and professional football)
    - Women's Athletic Scrapbooks 1982-1990
      - Vol. 1 1982-January 27, 1986 (Box 2, Reel 1)
      - Vol. 2 February 1, 1986-November 13, 1988 (Box 2, Reel 1)
      - Vol. 3 November 8, 1988-September 4, 1990 (Box 2, Reel 1)
      - Vol. 4 November 28, 1989-July 18, 1990, 120 pages (Box 2, Reel 2)
      - Vol. 5 August 23, 1990-March 18,1992, 286 pages (Box 2, Reel 2)
      - Vol. 6 September 7, 1990-December 31, 1992, 381 pages (Box 2, Reel 2)
      - Vol. 7 January 5, 1993-December 30, 1993, 286 pages (Box 2, Reel 3)
      - Vol. 8 January 6, 1994-December 22, 1994, 449 pages (Box 2, Reel 3)
      - Vol. 9 January 13, 1995-July 26, 1996, 150 pages (Box 2, Reel 3)
    - Women's Athletic Scrapbooks 1976-1992
      - Vol. 1 July 1976-December 1979 (Volume 1)
      - Vol. 2 January 1980-January 1981 (Volume 2)
      - Vol. 3 December 1981-November 1982 (Volume 3)
      - Vol. 4, (missing) (Volume 4)
      - Vol. 5 October 1983-June 1984 (Volume 5)
      - Vol. 6 September 1984-November 13, 1985 (Volume 6)
      - Vol. 7 November 15, 1985-April 2, 1987 (Volume 7)
      - Vol. 8 April 2, 1987-August 16, 1988 (Volume 8)
      - Vol. 9 September 8, 1988-November 30, 1989 (Volume 9)
      - Vol. 10 March 9, 1992-September 8, 1992 (Volume 10)
      - Vol. 11 September 30, 1992-March 30, 1993 (Volume 11)
  - Press Releases
    The Press Releases series consists of press releases produced by the Sports Information Office, 1943-1996 and continuing. Sometimes titled "Michigan Sports News," the releases were issued weekly. They provide information on upcoming games and events, give statistical summaries of the previous week's games and often a compilation of season statistics for teams and individuals. The press releases are arranged chronologically (by calendar year 1943-1979 and academic year beginning in 1979/80). Beginning in 1983/84 the year's releases are further subdivided by sport.
    - "Michigan Sports News"
      - 1943-1960 (Box 3)
        (one folder per calendar year)
      - 1961-1978 (Box 4)
      - 1979 January-August (Box 4)
      - 1979/80 (Box 5)
        (Academic year)
        - August-December (Box 5)
        - January-March (Box 5)
        - April-August (Box 5)
      - 1980/91
        - Football, 3 folders (Box 5)
        - September-December (Box 5)
        - January (Box 5)
        - February (Box 5)
        - March (Box 5)
        - April-July (Box 5)
      - 1981/82
        - August (Box 5)
        - September (Box 5)
        - October (Box 5)
        - November (Box 5)
        - December (Box 5)
        - January (Box 5)
        - February (Box 5)
        - March (Box 5)
        - April-July (Box 5)
      - 1982/83
        - August (Box 5)
        - September (Box 5)
        - October (Box 5)
        - November (Box 5)
        - December (Box 5)
        - January (Box 5)
        - February (Box 5)
        - March (Box 5)
        - April (Box 6)
        - May-June (Box 6)
      - 1983/84
        - Football (Box 6)
        - Basketball (Box 6)
        - Hockey, Baseball (Box 6)
        - Non-Revenue and Miscellaneous (Box 6)
        - Women's Sports (Box 6)
      - 1984/85
        - Football (Box 6)
        - Basketball, Hockey (Box 6)
        - Baseball (Box 6)
        - Non-Revenue, Miscellaneous (Box 6)
        - Women's Sports (Box 6)
      - 1985/86
        - Football (Box 6)
        - Basketball (Box 6)
        - Hockey (Box 6)
        - Baseball, Non-Revenue (Box 6)
        - Women's Sports (Box 6)
      - 1986/87
        - Football (Box 6)
        - Basketball (Box 6)
        - Hockey, Baseball (Box 6)
        - Non-Revenue (Box 6)
        - Women's Sports (Box 6)
      - 1987/88 (Box 7)
        - Football (Box 7)
        - Basketball, Hockey, Baseball (Box 7)
        - Non-Revenue and Miscellaneous (Box 7)
        - Women's Sports (Box 7)
      - 1988/89
        - Football (Box 7)
        - Basketball, Hockey, Baseball (Box 7)
        - Non-Revenue (Box 7)
        - Women's Sports (Box 7)
      - 1989/90
        - Baseball (Box 7)
        - Non-Revenue, Miscellaneous (Box 7)
        - Women's Sports (Box 7)
      - 1990/91
        (August-December and Fall sports missing)
        - January-June (Box 7)
        - Basketball, Hockey, Baseball (Box 7)
        - Non-Revenue (Box 7)
        - Women's Sports (Box 7)
      - 1991-1992
        - August-December (Box 7)
        - January-June (Box 7)
        - Football (Box 7)
        - Basketball (Box 7)
        - Hockey (Box 7)
        - Baseball (Box 7)
      - 1992/93
        - August-December (Box 7)
        - January-July (Box 7)
        - Football (Box 7)
        - Hockey (Box 7)
        - Baseball (Box 7)
      - 1993/94
        - August-December (Box 7)
        - January-April (Box 7)
        - Football (Box 56)
        - Hockey (Box 56)
        - Basketball (Box 56)
        - Baseball (Box 56)
      - 1994/95
        - September-December (Box 56)
        - January-July (Box 56)
        - Football (Box 56)
        - Hockey (Box 56)
        - Baseball (Box 56)
      - 1995/96
        - August-December (Box 56)
        - January-May (Box 56)
        - Cross Country (Box 56)
        - Football (Box 56)
        - Hockey (Box 56)
        - Baseball (Box 56)
        - Minor Sports (Box 56)
      - 1996/97
        - September-December 1996 (Box 56)
        - January-June, 1997 (Box 56)
        - Football (Box 56)
        - Hockey (Box 56)
        - Women's Sports (Box 56)
      - 1997/98
        - August-September 1997 (Box 56)
        - January-May 1998 (Box 56)
        - Football (Box 56)
        - Hockey (Box 56)
        - Baseball (Box 56)
  - Football
    - Photographs, 1879-
      - Team Photos, 1879-
        (Team photos in the Athletic Department. records for the following years are in outsize boxes 1-2, negatives and prints or contact sheets of team photos 1969-1994 are located in boxes 8-10 below. For a more complete, but not exhaustive, listing of football team photographs in the Athletic Department and other collections, see Appendix A, "Football Team Photographs")
        - 1879, 1884, 1885, 1887, 1888, 1891, 1893, 1894, 1898-1920 (Box 1)
        - 1921-1926, 1929-1962, 1964-1966, 1968-1971, 1973, 1977-1980, 1995, 2004 (Box 2)
      - Portraits and Action Photos, 1894-
        (see also box 3 outsize.)
        - 1892-1901 (Box 8)
        - ca.1900-1910 (Box 8)
        - "calendars" with player portraits 1901-1904 (Box 9)
        - 1898-circa 1905 "Niles Scrapbook" (Box 8)
          (magazine and newspaper photos of UM athletics; teams, individuals, and game action.)
        - 1901 (Box 8)
        - 1902 (Box 8)
        - 1903 (Box 8)
        - 1904-1905 (Box 8)
        - 1906-1907 (Box 8)
        - 1908-1909 (Box 8)
        - 1910-1912 (Box 8)
        - 1913 (Box 8)
        - 1914-1918 (Box 8)
        - 1919 (Box 8)
          (na copy negatives only)
        - 1920-1924 (Box 8)
        - 1925 (Box 8)
        - 1926 (Box 8)
        - 1927 (Box 8)
        - 1926-1927 (Box 8)
          (see also photo scrapbook in outsize box 9)
        - 1928 (Box 8)
        - 1929 (Box 8)
        - 1927-1930 (Box 8)
          (players identified, years not)
        - 1930 (Box 8)
        - 1931 (Box 9)
        - 1932 (Box 9)
        - 1933 (Box 9)
        - 1934 (Box 9)
        - 1934 Gerald Ford (Box 9)
          (3 posed action photos and later photos)
        - 1935 (Box 9)
        - 1936 (Box 9)
        - 1937 (Box 9)
        - 1938-1942 (Box 9)
          (photo scrapbook of Detroit News and Detroit Free Press picture day photos)
        - 1938 (Box 9)
        - 1939 (Box 9)
        - 1940 (Box 9)
        - 1940 Tom Harmon (Box 9)
        - 1940 airplane trip to California (Box 9)
        - 1941 (Box 9)
        - 1942 (Box 9)
        - 1943 (Box 9)
        - 1944 (Box 9)
        - 1945 (Box 9)
        - 1946 (Box 9)
        - 1947 (Box 9)
          (including 1948 Rose Bowl trip)
        - 1948 (Box 9)
        - 1947-1949 (Box 9)
        - circa 1938-1949 (Box 9)
          (opposing players and coaches, includes Buddy Young, Bernie Bierman, and Frank Leahy)
        - 1950-1959 (Box 9)
        - 1950 (Box 9)
        - 1950 "Snow Bowl" Ohio State game (Box 9)
          (prints and negs.)
        - 1951 (Box 9)
        - 1952 (Box 9)
        - 1953 (Box 9)
        - 1954 (Box 9)
        - 1955 (Box 9)
        - 1956 (Box 9)
        - 1956 Ron Kramer (Box 9)
          (prints and photocopies of News and Information Services action shots 1954-1956)
        - 1957 (Box 9)
        - 1958 (Box 10)
        - 1959 (Box 10)
        - 1959 Raeder's Raiders (Box 10)
        - 1960 (Box 10)
        - circa 1960-1969 (Box 10)
          (undated action shots)
        - 1961 (Box 10)
          (includes Dale Fisher color portraits)
        - 1962 (Box 10)
        - 1963 (Box 10)
        - 1964 (Box 10)
        - 1965 (Box 10)
          (includes color prints of Georgia game)
        - 1966 (Box 10)
          (includes negatives)
        - 1967 (Box 10)
          (includes print of coaches Bump and Pete Elliott)
        - 1968
          - Uniforms (Box 10)
            (prints, also includes prints of California game)
          - Uniforms (color slides) (Box 10)
          - Game Action (color slides) (Box 10)
          - Ron Johnson (Box 10)
      - Team and Individual Portraits, 1969-
        ("Team" = team photo, "portrait" = coat and tie player photos, "uniforms" = player photos in uniforms on picture day, negs=original negatives, cs=contact prints. Original negatives of Bob Kalmbach photos and contact sheets are in the Robert Kalmbach collection.)
        - 1969
          (includes color prints of OSU game)
          - Team (negs/cs) (Box 10)
          - Portraits (negs/cs) (Box 10)
          - Uniforms (prints) (Box 10)
          - Uniforms (negs) (Box 10)
          - Uniforms and coaches (color slides) (Box 10)
          - Game Action (Box 10)
            (including Rose Bowl)
        - 1970-1975 action, color and b/w negs. (Box 11)
        - 1970
          - Team (negs/cs) (Box 11)
          - Uniforms (prints), 2 folders (Box 11)
          - Uniforms (negs/cs) (Box 11)
            (includes Glazier negatives)
          - Game action (color slides) (Box 11)
        - 1971
          - Team (negs/cs) (Box 11)
          - Portraits (negs/cs) (Box 11)
          - Uniforms (prints) (Box 11)
          - Uniforms (negs/cs) (Box 11)
          - Uniforms (color slides) (Box 11)
          - Football Banquet (negs) (Box 11)
          - Game Action (prints, including Rose Bowl) (Box 11)
        - 1972
          - Team (negs/cs) (Box 11)
          - Portraits (negs) (Box 11)
          - Uniforms (prints) (Box 11)
          - Uniforms (negs/cs) (Box 11)
          - Uniforms (color slides) (Box 11)
          - Game action (color slides) (Box 11)
          - Gama Action (prints) (Box 11)
        - 1973
          - Team (negs/cs) (Box 11)
          - Portraits (negs/cs) (Box 11)
          - Uniforms (prints) (Box 11)
          - Uniforms (negs/cs) (Box 11)
            (includes color negatives)
          - Game Action (color slides) (Box 11)
        - 1974
          - Team (negs/cs) (Box 11)
          - Portraits (negs/cs) (Box 11)
          - Uniforms (prints) (Box 11)
          - Uniforms (negs/cs) (Box 11)
          - Uniforms (color slides) (Box 11)
          - Game Action (color slides) (Box 11)
          - Game Action (prints) (Box 11)
        - 1970-1979 game action (prints) (Box 11)
        - 1975
          - Team (negs/cs) (Box 72)
          - Portraits (negs/cs) (Box 72)
          - Uniforms (prints) (Box 72)
          - Uniforms (negs/cs) (Box 72)
          - Game Action (color slides) (Box 72)
          - Uniforms (color slides) (Box 72)
        - 1976
          - Team (negs/cs) (Box 72)
          - Portraits (negs/cs) (Box 72)
          - Uniforms (prints, b/w) (Box 72)
          - Uniforms (prints, color) (Box 72)
          - Uniforms (negs/cs) (Box 72)
          - Uniforms (color slides) (Box 72)
          - Game action (color slides) (Box 72)
          - Game Action, 3 folders (Box 72)
            (prints and negs. Includes some Rose Bowl game)
        - 1977
          - Team (negs/cs) (Box 72)
          - Portraits (negs) (Box 72)
          - Uniforms (prints/slides) (Box 72)
          - Uniforms (negs/cs) (Box 72)
          - Uniforms (prints) (Box 72)
            (also prints and negs of captains)
          - Game action (prints and negs), 2 folders (Box 72)
          - Game Action Rose Bowl (1/1/1978) (Box 72)
        - 1978
          - Team (negs/cs) (Box 72)
          - Uniforms (prints) (Box 72)
            (includes some game action and)
          - Uniforms (negs/cs) (Box 72)
          - Uniforms and Game Action (color slides) (Box 72)
          - Rose Bowl action, Charles White disputed fumble 1979 (Box 72)
        - 1979
          - Team (negs/cs) (Box 73)
          - Portraits (negs/cs) (Box 73)
          - Uniforms (negs/cs) (Box 73)
          - Uniforms (prints) (Box 73)
          - Coaches (color prints) (Box 73)
          - Uniforms and Game Action (color slides) (Box 73)
          - Game Action (prints) (Box 73)
        - 1980
          - Team (negs/cs) (Box 73)
          - Portraits (negs/cs) (Box 73)
          - Uniforms (prints) (Box 73)
          - Uniforms (negs/cs) (Box 73)
          - Game action (prints) (Box 73)
          - Uniforms and Game Action (color slides) (Box 73)
        - 1981
          - Team (b/w print/negs/cs) (Box 73)
          - Portraits (negs/cs) (Box 73)
          - Uniforms (prints) (Box 73)
          - Uniforms (negs/cs) (Box 73)
          - Game Action (prints) (Box 73)
          - Uniforms an Game Action (color slides) (Box 73)
        - 1982
          - Team (b/w print/negs/cs) (Box 73)
          - Uniforms (prints) (Box 73)
          - Uniforms (negs/cs) (Box 73)
          - Portraits (negs/cs) (Box 73)
          - Game action (prints) (Box 73)
          - Uniforms (color slides) (Box 73)
        - 1983
          - Team (b/w & color print/negs/cs) (Box 254)
          - Portraits (negs/cs) (Box 254)
          - Uniforms (prints) (Box 254)
          - Uniforms (negs/cs) (Box 254)
          - Game Action (prints) (Box 254)
          - Game Action and uniforms (color slides), 2 folders (Box 254)
        - 1984
          - Team (b/w & color print/negs/cs) (Box 254)
          - Portraits (negs/cs) (Box 254)
          - Uniforms (prints and color slides) (Box 254)
          - Uniforms (negs/cs) (Box 254)
          - Game Action (Box 254)
        - 1985
          - Team (b/w & color prints) (Box 254)
          - Uniforms (c/s some prints and slides) (Box 254)
          - Portraits (negs & cs) (Box 254)
          - Game action (Kalmbach cs) (Box 254)
        - 1986
          - Team (prints and cs) (Box 254)
          - Uniforms (cs & some slides) (Box 254)
          - Portraits (cs) (Box 254)
          - Portraits (color prints) (Box 254)
          - Game Action (Kalmbach cs) (Box 254)
          - Game Action, Rose Bowl (Box 254)
            (slides, by Paul Jasienski)
        - 1987
          - Team (c/s, freshman team negatives) (Box 254)
          - Uniforms(cs, some prints and slides) (Box 254)
          - Portraits (cs) (Box 254)
          - Game Action (prints, includes aerial shot of 1988 Hall of Fame Bowl) (Box 254)
          - Game Action (negs. & cs) (Box 254)
            (by Jim Kerringer Photography)
        - 1988
          - Team (prints & cs) (Box 264)
          - Uniforms (cs and some prints and slides) (Box 264)
          - Uniforms (prints and slides) (Box 264)
          - Game Action (prints and slides, including Rose Bowl) (Box 264)
        - 1989
          - Team (prints and cs) (Box 264)
          - Uniforms (coaching staff only) (prints and cs) (Box 264)
          - Portraits (Freshmen only) (cs) (Box 264)
          - Game Action (prints and slides) (Box 264)
          - Game Action-Spring Game (prints) (Box 264)
        - 1990
          - Team (prints & cs) (Box 264)
          - Uniforms (cs & some negatives) (Box 264)
          - Uniforms (slides) (Box 264)
          - Portraits (cs) (Box 264)
          - Football coaches and staff (prints and cs) (Box 264)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 264)
            (includes prints used in recruiting brochure)
          - Game Action (prints), 3 folders (Box 264)
          - Gator Bowl MVPs at M Stadium (negatives) (Box 264)
        - 1991
          - Team and Staff (Box 264)
          - Uniforms (cs and slides), 2 folders (Box 264)
          - Portraits (cs) (Box 264)
          - Desmond Howard (Box 264)
        - 1992
          - Team and Staff (prints and cs) (Box 264)
          - Uniforms (cs) (Box 264)
          - Portraits (freshmen only) (cs) (Box 264)
          - Game action (Box 264)
        - 1993
          - Team photo and Staff (Box 280)
          - Uniforms (cs and slides) (Box 280)
          - Portraits (cs) (Box 280)
          - Game Action (Box 280)
        - 1994
          - Team and Staff (Box 280)
          - Uniforms (Box 280)
          - Portraits (Box 280)
          - Game Action (Box 280)
          - Game Action Holiday Bowl (Box 280)
        - 1995
          - Team and Staff (color negs of team, prints, cs) (Box 280)
          - Uniforms (cs) (Box 280)
          - Portraits (cs) (Box 280)
          - Uniforms (Box 280)
          - Game Action (Box 280)
        - 1996
          - Team Photo and staff (prints and cs) (Box 280)
          - Uniforms (cs) (Box 280)
          - Portraits (cs) (Box 280)
          - Game Action (Box 280)
        - 1997
          - Team and Staff (Box 281)
          - Uniforms (cs) (Box 281)
          - Portraits (C) (Box 281)
          - Game Action (prints) (Box 281)
          - Game Action (Kalmbach), 1 folders (Box 281)
          - Rose Bow and National Championship celebration and parade (Box 281)
        - 1998
          - Team and Staff (Box 281)
          - Uniforms (Cs) (Box 281)
          - Game Action (Kalmbach, b/w prints) (Box 281)
          - Game Action (Kalmbach color prints) (Box 281)
          - Game Action (Lad Strayer and others, color prints) (Box 281)
        - 1999 (Box 282)
          - Team and Staff (Box 282)
          - Uniforms (cs) (Box 282)
          - Portraits (cs) (Box 282)
          - Game Action, 1 folders (Box 282)
        - 2000
          - Team Photo and staff (Box 282)
          - Uniforms and Portraits (cs) (Box 282)
          - Freshmen -- uniforms and portraits (cs) (Box 282)
          - Game Action (Box 282)
            (Bob Kalmbach prints, Wisconsin game)
        - 2001
          - Team Photo and action (prints and cds) (Box 282)
        - 2002
          - Game Action, 1 folders; 2 folders (Box 282)
        - 2004 Team Photo (Box 282)
        - 2005 Team Photo (Box 282)
        - 2006 Team Photo (Box 282)
      - Digital Photos, 1999- (Box 282)
      - 1999 (Bill Wood photos) (Box 272)
        (includes Notre Dame, Rice, Purdue, Northwestern, Ohio State)
      - 1999 (John Gilman Photos) (Box 272)
        (includes Illinois, Ohio State, Orange Bowl)
      - 2000 (Bill Wood photos, with additional photos by Martin Vloet) (Box 272)
        (includes Bowling Green, Rice, Wisconsin, Indiana, Michigan State, Penn State)
      - 2000 (John Gilman photos) (Box 272)
        (Wisconsin, Purdue, Ohio State, Auburn, Florida Citrus Bowl Conference)
      - 2001 (John Gilman Photos) (Box 273)
        (includes Western Michigan, Illinois, Ohio State, Tennessee)
      - 2001 (Bill McKenna Photos)
        (includes Miami of Ohio, Western Michigan, Illinois, Purdue, Michigan State, Minnesota, Wisconsin, Ohio State)
        - 2001 (Amir Gamzu Digital Images) (Box 273)
          (includes Miami of Ohio, Washington, Western Michigan, Purdue, Michigan State, Minnesota, Ohio State)
        - 1996-2000 (Slides from Getty Images) (Box 273)
          (includes Correspondence, Player Action, Game Photos)
          [copyright restricted]
        - 2002 (John Gilman and Bill McKenna Digital Photos) (Box 274)
          (includes Notre Dame, Utah, Michigan State)
        - 2002 Amir Gamzu, Tom Wagner, and Brad Mills Photos (Box 274)
          (Washington, Western Michigan, Utah, Penn State, Iowa, Michigan State, Wisconsin, Ohio State, Outback Bowl, Penn State (Bill McKenna))
        - 2003 (John Gilman, Joe Arcure, and Pete Stanger Digital Photos (Box 274)
          (includes Houston, Notre Dame, Ohio State, Rose Bowl vs. Southern California, Illinois, Michigan State)
        - 2003 (Amir Gamzu and Eric Bronson Digital Images (Box 274)
          (includes: Central Michigan, Houston, Notre Dame, Oregon, Indiana, Iowa, Minnesota, Illinois)
        - 2003 (Bill McKenna Photos), 2 volumes (Box 275)
          (Houston, Notre Dame, Indiana, Purdue, Michigan, State, Northwestern, Ohio State, Rose Bowl vs. Southern California)